♪
[deep inhale]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Could you stop the camera?
[CAMERAMAN 22A] Sorry?
[SUNG JINWOO] Stop the camera,
or I'll break it.
Oh!
No problem, sir!
[thumping]
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Hunter Sung.
What are you planning
to do with Byung-gu?
I asked you a damn question!
What are you doing?
What I have to.
We're running out of time.
[gasps]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
Arise.
♪
[SUGIMOTO REIJI]
The chairman has called
for the execution of plan nine.
Are you ready?
Are you insane?
Sending us back to that island
is sending us to our deaths!
You'd understand if you'd seen
that freak in the flesh!
He killed Goto-san,
like it was nothing.
The new ant is dead.
[both gasp]
One of their hunters
was able to take it down.
[HOSHINO MINORU]
They killed it? Really?
[SUGIMOTO REIJI] Do you
still insist on staying behind?
[rain splattering]
[CHOI JONG-IN]
A skill that lets you raise
and command the dead.
So it wasn't your ordinary
summoning magic, then.
Byung-gu.
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
A voice called out to me.
It was Hunter Min,
saying I should
use his power to save her.
♪
[paper rustling]
I can tell he was
a remarkable person.
Healing Hunter Cha
without even a word from me.
[gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO] He was
the best of us, wasn't he?
[gasps]
[CAMERAMAN 22A]
I get why he wouldn't want
video evidence of this.
[CHOI JONG-IN] The fiercer the
battle, the stronger he grows.
What a terrifying ability.
[MA DONGWOOK] But now,
what happens to Byung-gu Min?
[BAEK YOONHO]
Hunter Sung.
If you carry on as a hunter,
I have no doubt
Byung-gu's healing magic
will serve you well.
♪
Thing is,
he always hated fighting.
He only signed on
for this raid.
Because he believed
it would be his final mission.
Please keep it that way.
[SUNG JINWOO]
You grabbed my shoulder again.
[gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO] Just like back
at the red gate incident.
The only difference now,
is it's not an order,
it's an earnest plea
for your friend.
You don't have to worry.
I was thinking the same thing.
♪
Release extraction.
[gasps]
♪
[whimpering]
[sniffles]
[BAEK YOONHO]
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
How are they still alive?
[SUGIMOTO REIJI]
Hunter Sung arrived
and proceeded
to defeat the new variant.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
I can see that, idiot!
How is he there?
You said he decided
not to participate in the raid!
[SUGIMOTO REIJI] Based on
the magic power readings,
all we can say is
he appeared out of nowhere.
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
This is a nightmare.
And on the heels of losing
seven of the ten
S-ranks we sent!
[SUGIMOTO REIJI]
Chairman, do you still want us
to go through with plan nine?
Any further casualties
will undercut our ability
to respond to domestic gates
and could have
lasting ramifications
on the global balance of power.
What's your call?
[MATSUMOTO SHIGEO]
We're pulling out.
Withdraw immediately.
[SUGIMOTO REIJI]
Understood, sir.
[phone beeping]
[growls]
[clattering]
[panting]
[growling]
♪
[grunts]
Why are they after us now?
They weren't before!
-[grunts]
-Do I look like I know?
I thought the queen
was dead already!
That's your answer right there!
[explosions]
With no one to lead them,
they're all over the place!
Stay sharp!
They can't reach the mainland!
Ain't gettin' past us!
Now let's show these bugs
what the Knights Guild can do!
You're givin' me strength
to keep fighting!
♪
Hurry!
The ants are everywhere!
[panting]
♪
Isn't this a prime shitshow.
[SEO JIWOO] The ants are going
berserk trying to flee,
and most of them are heading
straight toward the mainland.
We should leave before they
block our route out of here!
I couldn't agree with you more.
Let's board and take off.
What about Hunter Sung?
He told us
he wanted to stay behind
to take care of the remaining
ants and eggs.
[CHOI JONG-IN]
It's tough to admit,
but in our condition,
we'd just slow him down
if we stuck around.
And while she's no longer
in mortal danger,
we should have the medic team
examine Hunter Cha
as soon as possible.
♪
[fire roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO]
I get experience points
for smashing unhatched eggs.
Lucky me.
♪
[sword clanking]
[electricity crackling]
♪
[rumbling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Demon Monarch Sword, heh.
Damn right it is.
Feel kinda bad
for not using it earlier.
All right, guys.
Knock yourselves out.
[Iron roaring]
♪
Level 100.
I've hit it.
[static]
[sword clanking]
[SUNG JINWOO]
He may be dead,
but I can still feel
an immense aura.
Arise.
♪
[gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Why is it all dark?
I can't sense anything.
Did something happen
with the extraction?
[gasps]
I'm back.
♪
[rumbling]
[fire crackling]
[SUNG JINWOO] Thought I
botched it for a second there.
Guess we're good.
Let's go wake
your pals up, too.
[BERU]
My king.
[gasps]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Did you just talk?
[BERU]
Yes.
[SUNG JINWOO] None of the other
shadows talk, so why can he?
[BERU]
Please grant me a name.
I beg you.
[SUNG JINWOO]
"General" rank?
Never seen that before.
Is speech a perk of this rank?
Actually, I've got
a bigger question.
You know I was the one
who killed you, right?
So, do you still wish
to follow my lead?
[BERU]
I do, for I did not die.
By your hand, Master,
I was reborn.
I am filled with...
overwhelming joy.
I swear to serve you
for eternity.
So, please,
grant me a name.
[gasps]
[echoing]
Beru.
The name I grant you is Beru.
I am honored, Master.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Now, where was I?
Arise.
♪
[MALE HUNTER 25A] Guess they
got past the hunters at sea.
We're the last line of defense!
Stop them here or die trying!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
How the hell do we
fight these things?
All tanks get in front!
Don't let them reach
the cities, whatever you do!
[all screaming]
[indistinct chatter]
[SUNG JINWOO]
That's a lotta ants.
[BERU] They cannot organize
themselves without a leader,
so all 4,000 are scattering.
[SUNG JINWOO]
There are still that many?
Can you shave
that number down for me?
[BERU]
If that is your wish, my king,
you need only say the word.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Go.
♪
[explosion]
[thuds]
All right, nice job!
These things are dangerous!
Don't be a hero,
just take down one at a time!
If everyone works together,
we can survive this!
Mister Song!
♪
[LEE JOOHEE]
Are you okay? What happened?
I'm not really sure.
♪
[LEE JOOHEE]
That blue light.
[SONG CHIYUL]
I could be wrong, but...
I think that light saved us.
Jinwoo must've sent it.
♪
[LIM TAE-GYU]
There are too damn many!
Why aren't you
lighting them up?
If I did,
I'd wreck the helicopter!
♪
[creaking]
This is the worst.
Not a lot we can do
to help in midair.
♪
[grunting]
-[cracking]
-[gasps]
[shattering]
[all gasp]
♪
[electricity crackling]
Huh?
[BAEK YOONHO] We were
saved twice in one day,
by the same man.
♪
They should be able
to make it back now.
[crowd cheering]
[GO GUNHEE]
And so...
the ants that managed to break
through the island's perimeter
were held off by the scores
of brave hunters
standing guard in the field,
their efforts significantly
minimizing the damage
to the mainland.
All but one of our country's
S-ranks returned to us.
And, Hunter Cha,
who remained unconscious,
was safely transported
to a hospital.
It was a hard-fought battle
and not everyone
walked away from it.
But despite the casualties,
the emergent threat
from the island
was successfully neutralized.
The fourth Jeju Island raid
to clear the dungeon break,
ended in our victory.
[COMMANDER 25A] We've got
more visitors from far abroad.
That's two days straight now.
They're just about
within firing range.
[CREW 25A] Jianzhang, I'll
notify the mages on standby.
Preparing to intercept
the incoming ants!
-Sailors, man your stations!
-Belay that order.
[COMMANDER 25A]
It seems China's hero wants
a little bit of exercise.
[Liu Zhigang sighs]
[LIU ZHIGANG]
Can't sit around all day.
And here they come.
Hao ba, let's send some
vermin to a watery grave.
[inhales deeply]
[growls]
[explosions]
If I'd gotten a crack
at the black ant
instead of that
Jeen-whatever guy,
might've actually had some fun.
A shame.
[ANNOUNCER 25A]
Several days have passed
since the successful
Jeju Island raid,
and a memorial has been erected
in honor of the lives lost,
with a large crowd
coming to pay their respects.
And here we see S-rank hunter,
Jinwoo Sung,
approaching the monument.
His contributions to the raid
were immense to say the least,
and it's arguable that we would
not have succeeded without him.
Some are calling him a hero...
[FEMALE 25A]
But at the same time,
there are more
critical voices asking
whether there would
have been fewer casualties
had Hunter Sung
agreed to participate
from the very beginning.
[footfall]
♪
[BAEK YOONHO]
Please hold your head high.
No matter
what the public thinks,
the one who ended
this tragedy...
was you, Hunter Sung.
♪
[gasps]
Hm?
I doubt anything I say
could express my sincere
and unwavering gratitude.
But still, please allow me
to thank you for your service.
No, sir.
If I had just left
for the raid a bit sooner,
then maybe I could've
saved Hunter Min.
You did save
five other S-ranks, though.
Not to mention
the remaining defenders
and the citizens
who would have died
had they fallen.
You should be proud,
not ashamed.
I give you my word
that you will be rewarded
however you wish...
in due time.
-I appreciate it.
-Hm.
[GO GUNHEE]
Now, I was wondering,
about your plans
for the future.
-[SUNG JINWOO] The future, sir?
-[GO GUNHEE] Yes.
[GO GUNHEE]
Thanks to this raid,
your power
has been demonstrated
on an international level.
I doubt the public will
leave you alone anytime soon.
And what
the Association can't ignore
is that you'll be approached
by all sorts of people
with various motives.
Which is why I feel
the need to ask you.
Hunter Sung,
just what will you do
with all the power you wield?
When you fight,
whose battles will they be?
♪
I've been thinking about
starting up a guild of my own.
[JUNG YOONTAE] How the hell did
we get stuck with cleanup duty
on the day of the
memorial ceremony?
Well, dumbass, maybe because
this is important stuff, too.
Someone's gotta
kill the stragglers
and collect the resources.
And gettin' delegated
to tie up the loose ends
shows they trust me.
[JUNG YOONTAE]
But...
But nothin', kid.
[sword slashing]
[thuds]
A real man does the job
he's given, nice and smooth.
And he doesn't bitch about
doin' it either.
You are so awesome!
[all gasp]
Hold it!
Jeju Island
is off-limits to civilians!
-Identify yourself!
-[speaking foreign language]
[gasps]
Look.
Whoever you are.
This ain't an open invitation,
you're not supposed to--
[heart thumping]
[thudding]
What did you do?
I just had them
take a little nap.
All that noise
was bothering me.
In any case,
was it him we sensed?
[MAN 25A] Yeah,
it was definitely his power.
[OLD MAN 25A]
I don't know why he'd willingly
lend that power to humans.
It's very strange.
[MAN 25A]
His behavior is nothing new,
but if you're curious.
You could just
ask him yourself.
If given the chance perhaps.
[snaps fingers]
We got one answer at least.
[electricity crackling]
Let us return
with this knowledge.
[MAN 25A]
Wait, isn't one of them here?
[OLD MAN 25A] I think this area
would be best left to him.
[MAN 25A] In other words,
you don't want to get involved.
The hunt will commence
as we planned it.
That hasn't changed.
[exhales]
Yeah.
I guess it really isn't worth
the extra trouble.
♪
[MAN 25A]
Quite the stench, though.
She'd be less than pleased
if she caught a whiff of this.
♪
[SUNG JINWOO]
Traffic sucks.
[YOO JINHO] Did you, uh,
ask about the guild?
Yeah, Chairman Go gave us
his approval, so we're good.
Wow!
Just like that?
I'll get straight to work
finding us an office, then!
-[HAN SONG-YI] A guild?
-Excuse you!
Jinwoo, you have to promise
that you'll hire me, okay?
I'll be a devoted guildmate!
[YOO JINHO] This is an
important business discussion!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Okay, okay, bye, hanging up.
[scoffs]
Those two.
For real though,
the hell's going on
with this traffic?
♪
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
[GO GUNHEE]
Hunter Sung. It's Chairman Go.
Was there a problem
with the guild, sir?
[GO GUNHEE]
No, I'm calling about a gate.
[SUNG JINWOO] You said
it's down this highway?
[GO GUNHEE] It's a B-rank
but it'll be a while
before our hunters
can get there.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Ugh, but I can't go without
the Association's permission.
[GO GUNHEE]
Haha, who do you think
you're speaking to right now?
The big man in charge.
[indistinct chatter]
[WORKER 25A]
One vehicle at a time, please!
The association
needs to fix this stat.
[MOTORIST 25A]
Where are the hunters at?
What? The hunters are caught
in all this traffic, too?
Then, what's the plan?
Hey, did you just...
Rude.
Ah?
Hey, I'm here
to close the gate.
Right, Manager Woo just told me
but, you're the only hunter
who's arrived so far,
and it might be a minute
before the other ones show up--
-Let me solo it.
-Sir! Wait!
I know it's only B-rank,
but it is still risky
to go alone.
[gasps]
[electricity crackling]
It's a red gate!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Yep.
This is a red gate.
[rain splattering]
I don't understand
how this keeps happening to me.
The exit's closed
till I beat the boss,
and I have no clue
how far this forest goes.
[sighs]
Should've called Mom
to tell her I was gonna be late
before coming in here.
[growling]
Well, if this is all there is,
it won't take long.
[electricity crackling]
♪
[roaring]
[electricity crackling]
♪
Now, let's try
to make this quick.
♪
I saw he came to the service.
[CHA HAE-IN]
This raid proved
that I still have
a lot to learn.
I was no help in the end.
My mission was
to save our country
and I had to be saved.
But, not him.
I want to catch up to him.
♪
I want to stand at his side.
And to do that...
I need to get stronger.
[sword clanking]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Hunters are born to hunt,
and in dungeons where survival
is far from guaranteed,
they have to be prepared
to become the prey.
See, the tides can change
at any given moment.
♪
They're always one wrong move
away from death,
but never willing to back down.
Doesn't matter how strong,
or how numerous the enemies.
♪
Because they've all got
something to fight for.
To protect their family.
To uphold their ideals.
To prove who they are.
♪
To defy fate.
[roaring]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Hunters will continue to hunt.
And not a single one
is ready to stop.
[footfall]
[rain splattering]
[thunder rumbling]
♪
Let's move on
to the next target.